Data

The speech data are taken from the fluent-speech-corpus [https://www.kaggle.com/datasets/tommyngx/fluent-speech-corpus?resource=download]. This dataset consists of several speakers pronouncing a set of fixed commands. The speaker ID 7B4XmNppyrCK977p was selected, and all sentences from this speaker were loaded. Sentences shorter than 2 seconds were discarded.

Noise samples are frog sounds taken from the Environmental Sound Classification 50 dataset [https://www.kaggle.com/datasets/mmoreaux/environmental-sound-classification-50], which contains samples of various environmental sounds with a fixed duration of 5 seconds.